things like deep fakes these are all
within the realm of AI but how do they
fit within each other how are they
related to each other we're going to
take a look at that in this video and
try to explain how all these
Technologies relate and how we can use
them first off a little bit of a
disclaimer I'm going to have to simplify
some of these Concepts in order to not
make this video last for a week so those
of you that are really deep experts in
the field apologies in advance but we're
going to try to make this simple and and
that will involve some generalizations
first of all let's start with AI
artificial intelligence is basically
trying to simulate with a computer
something that would match or exceed
human intelligence what is intelligence
well it could be a lot of different
things but generally we tend to think of
it as the ability to learn to infer and
to reason things like that so that's
what we're trying to do in the broad
field of AI of artificial intelligence
and if we look at a timeline of AI it