everybody's talking about artificial
intelligence these days AI machine
learning is another Hot Topic are they
the same thing or are they different and
if so what are those differences and
deep learning is another one that comes
into play I actually did a video on
these three artificial intelligence
machine learning and deep learning and
talked about where they fit and there
were a lot of comments on that and I
read those comments and I'd like to
address some of the most frequently
asked questions so that we clear up some
of the myths and misconceptions around
this in addition something else has
happened since that video was recorded
and that is this the absolute explosion
of this area of generative AI things
like large language models and chat Bots
have seemed to be taking over the world
we see them everywhere really
interesting technology uh and then also
things like deep fakes these are all
within the realm of AI but how do they
fit within each other how are they